

Phattanothai Pukham



Personal Information

Nick Name
Military Status
Date of Availaility

Fluke Reservist Immediately

I don't have much work experience. But I am ready to learn and develop. I'm the type of person who likes a challenge. easy to get along with I like to try new things and develop myself all the time.

I hope that we will have the opportunity to work together.

Contect

Tel Email Address 0875683762 zeref38@gmail.com 96 Moo.6 Tambon Thanthong, Amphur Phan, Chiang Rai

57250

Github

https://github.com/phattanotai https://portfolios.gracia.tech

Skills

Website

Graphic Design
Fair

UX/UI Design
Fair

Coding

Fluent

Database

Good

Server

Standard

Research

Excellent

EDUCATION

2012-2016 Bachelor of Science Program in Computer Science

Suan Sunandha Rajabhat University

GPA 3.21

2009-2016 Pali language

Wat Paknam Bhasicharoen

WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 - Present Freelance Full Stack Developer (Web App,

Mobile App, REST API)

10 Nov. 2020 - 2021 Full Stack Developer Full-Time (Web App,

Mobile App, REST API) at OTEN INNOVATION, (Remote Work)

1 Jul. 2020 - 8 Nov. 2020 Developer Full-Time (Web App, REST API,

LINE Bot) at GWT, Chiang Rai

1 Jul. 2019 - 30 Jun. 2020 Programmer Full-Time (Web App, Mobile App,

tcp server, REST API) at WGT, Chiang Rai

http://wgtgps.net/login

1 May 2017 – 30 Apr. 2019 Fort Mengraimaharaj Hospital, Chiang Rai

ABILITIES

Coding Python, Nodejs, PHP, SQL, C/C++, C#, Java, Javascript,

Typescript

Flask, Express, Slim, Nestjs

Angular, Vuejs, React, Nextjs, React Native, Ionic, Jquery

Bootstrap, Material-ui

DevExtreme, Rxjs, Redux, Vuex

One Signal, Pusher, Selenium, Graphql, Apollo, Threejs

Sequelize, TypeORM, Mongoose

Google Map, Leaflet Map, Longdo Map

Polling, Server Sent Event, Websocket, SocketIO

Integrate Api e.g. dlt, scg, cpf, Integrate gamebrand e.g.

sexy, pg, sbobet send sms email, line api

Database Postgresql, Mysql, Sql Server, Mongodb, Redis, SQLite

Config Replication Master and Slave Server Postgis, Geo, Stored Procedure, Database trigger

Server Ubuntu, Window Server, Nginx, Load Balance, Cluster Mode,

Kubernetes, Docker, Docker Swarm, Kong Api Gateway, Cloudflare, GCP, AWS, Netlify, CircleCI, GitlabCI,

Prometheus, Grafana, gRPC, RabbitMQ

Tools Gitlab, Bitbucket, Github, Jira, Asana, Gather Town, Slack

Research Microservice, Microfrontend, Service Mesh Isito, ArgoCD,

Jenkins, Apache Kafka, Terraform, Ansible Elasticsearch, Opensearch, LevelDB, Firebase Robot Framework, Cypress, Figma, Zeplin

Flutter, Laravel, Spring Boot, ASP.Net Core, FastAPI, Rust,

Golang, Solidity, Wab3, Ethers.js, Kotlin, Swift, Unity,

Facebook API, WebRTC, WASM